在程序运行的时候，我知道你们很可能厌倦了盯着无聊的假数据而且
On app launch, I know that you're probably tired of seeing the dummy data and
希望每一刻点击刷新来获取实时信息
needing to hit the refresh button for real data every single time.
我会告诉你们如何自动显示当前设置对应的数据
I'm going to show you how to display the data using the current settings each
即在每次Activity被载入后自动刷新。在ForecastFragment中
time the activity is loaded. In forecast fragment,
我们重构了一下代码以便当刷新按钮被选中的时候
we just refactored the code so that when the refresh button is selected,
我们可以调用这个辅助方法，updateWeather。现在这里是那个辅助方法，
we call this helper_method, updateWeather. Now that it's in a helper method,
我们也可以从onStart方法中调用它。我们覆盖了onStart() 这样
we can also call it from the onStart method. We over write onStart so
每当Fragment启动的时候都会刷新一次。
that the refresh happens whenever the fragment starts.
这会使天气信息显示出来。我们会在下一节课学习关于onStart的所有东西，和
This will cause the weather data to appear. We'll learn all about onStart, and
Android生命周期的其他部分。现在
the rest of the android life cycle in the next lesson. At this point,
我们也可以移除我们在onCreateView方法里的所有假数据。
we can also remove all the fake data that we had in the onCreateView method.
然后向ArrayAdapter传递一个空的ArrayList。现在我们可以对其进行测试了。
Then we pass in an empty array list to the ArrayAdapter. Now we can test this.
我们需要确定这是第一个启动的程序而且
We need to make sure that this is the first app launch and
并未正在运行。如果已经运行了，杀掉。
that it wasn't already running. So if it's already running, kill it.
然后点击重开。
And then tap to open the app,
然后你应该立刻看见真实的天气数据。在设置菜单下，我们
and then you should see the actual weather data immediately. Under settings we
可以更改位置去相对应的邮编。当我们点击ok，
can change the location to be the pairs postal code. We hit OK, and
会跳回主菜单，然后我们可以看见天气数据是更新过的。
then return to the main list, and then we see that the weather data has updated.